Introduction
Chapter 1 Seeing Life Through the Lens of Possibility
Chapter 2 Giving Others an “A” and Transforming Relationships
Chapter 3 Rewriting the Rules That Shape Experience
Chapter 4 Shifting from Scarcity to Abundance in Everyday Life
Chapter 5 Becoming a Contribution and Finding Meaning
Chapter 6 Leading by Enrollment—Inviting Others into Possibility
Chapter 7 The Practice of “Being the Board”—Reclaiming Agency
Chapter 8 Giving Way to Passion—Letting Energy Lead
Chapter 9 Lighting a Spark—The Transformative Power of Story
Chapter 10 Creating Frameworks for Possibility—Structures That Set Us Free
Chapter 11 Transforming the World—Ripples of Possibility
Conclusion